backlinksolutions.com 2012-10-04

# Privacy Policy - Backlinksolutions.com

#### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

#### The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on BacklinkSolutions.com website. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

First Name :  
Last Name :  
E-Mail :  
Address :  
Address cont :  
City :  
State :  
Zip Code :  
Country :  
Phone :  
Fax :  

#### The Way We Use Information:

All information collected is only used to keep track of our accounts. In the near future this information will also be used to send out affiliate cheques for those members that sign up for our affiliate program.

#### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your account and simply edit your personal information. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

#### How To Contact Us:
